Jhal Hello
Hello Everyone Today we are going to tell you about
Sharp Lanka vs Tata AIG's
medical shop for Max Bupa. If we talk about longer term then
in Max Bupa you can avail cover up to Rs 3 lakh crore
whereas Yuvraj can subscribe from Rs 1 lakh
to Rs 50 lakh for hospitalization. If we
talk about medical treatment then it
covers scaled treatment whereas
Tata AIG covers 541 days treatment.
Organ donor can avail up to Rs 1 lakh benefit in both the companies like Sameer
and Ritesh Max Bupa Cares
benefits
and the best thing is that you
can subscribe for a limited time. For example if you subscribe then you
can avail cover up to Rs 1 lakh that too. If you do
not subscribe then you can
appoint a medical and after
subscribing
that fee you get coverage after Rs 520.
No claim bonus.
50% in both the companies. If we talk about emergency ambulance then
in Max Bupa you can avail cover up to Rs 12 lakh
whereas in Tata AIG you can subscribe for
Ayurvedic treatment. So in one company
now there are different styles of subscription in Max Bupa.  Till then if we
talk about the game balance then you can subscribe, you can
subscribe whereas
in Tata AIG you can claim up to 5 lakhs
so treatment which means
any situation in which the patient
cannot visit the hospital, it is
not available in the hospital,
in both these companies the appointment of consumer durables
such items are not available items,
this cotton subscription is
not done by any company but if you see the
difference in the city then you will understand this whereas
Tata Magic is that you do
not have to subscribe,
you will have to get the test done from the tests given by these people in the subscription
and you can spend 5000 for individual and
maximum 1000 for family floater,
Tiger this Pawan can do
maximum, you can subscribe to the channel in
treatment of the appointment of the youth
who is appointed on your routes, home
subscription is not available
whereas in Tata Global available
one condition is that the disease should be
diagnosed in India which is
Tata AIG  You can subscribe to the plan of Rs. 1000 but you get
appointment and treatment benefits
in Max Bupa whereas you can subscribe to Tata AIG plan
and you can get unlimited treatment, there is no
limit in this you can subscribe
only for the OPD treatment. The
treatment cover of Tiger Bir
Video is
an accidental death benefit rider.
This is not covered in Max Bupa whereas in Tata AB
if you have a policy and death occurs due to an accident
then the policy holder gets the
full benefit and his nominee gets it. These were
not available for different styles of travel. If
you have a plan in Max Bupa then you will
not get this benefit. It means that
any such treatment hospital is far
away from your family and the admission charges up to Rs.
1000 for travelling home. Whereas if we
talk about appointment then it is for
Shreya Ghoshal and three years whereas Tata
Dhindsa is for 2 years and three years discount on the other side.
Max Bupa has 7.5% subscription and
5% subscription. There is competition
between the two products, both are very good
products, you can choose your product as per your convenience.  You
can select it. If you
liked the video, we keep bringing information on such issues, so
please like and subscribe to our channel.
Thank you for
watching.